<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jhwaffles</title>
    <description>Assorted Projects and Posts</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:37:19 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:37:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator><item>
        <title>Berry Shake Recipe</title>
        <description>&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/layer_juice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Berry and Greens shake&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbsp almond butter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbsp cocoa powder&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 tbsp chia seeds&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups unsweetened almond milk (oat milk, coconut milk ok)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups water&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups power greens blend (spinach, chard, kale). I roughly do 4 handfuls.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cups frozen berries. I roughly do 4 handfuls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I add the ingredients generally in sequence. Chia seeds should be soaked in water beforehand so they have time to expand/soften before blending. Makes roughly 4 servings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><description>&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/layer_juice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Berry and Greens shake&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/Shake_Recipe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/Shake_Recipe/</guid></item><item>
        <title>Visiting Parents</title>
        <description>&lt;!-- &lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;eight Loss&lt;/p&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dad had many reasons for wanting to lose weight. He would always get comments from friends or visiting relatives, including my grandparents when they were around. Health was a big factor - his doctor said he needed to lose 20 lbs to be in better condition. Most of all, he wanted to look better in photos - Nothing makes him happier than when someone leave a positive comment in family photos. So in other words he wanted to shut down the haters, improve health, and look good. I should mention that my dad is retired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hearing that my dad was struggling, Cynthia wondered if she could come up with a program to help my dad improve his condition. It seemed like he was genuinely interested in losing weight but was discouraged by previous attempts. In the midst of a sunny hike in the Oakland hills, we discussed putting my parents on an eating “program” with a focus on losing weight. I should note my mom was also interested, not because she needed to lose weight but because she did not want to miss out (FOMO). Coming off of a recent “program” for ourselves (Link), we talked of guiding my parents through a similar program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-plan&quot;&gt;The Plan&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is what we came up with: my parents would go on a meal plan crafted by Cynthia for 3 weeks. Cynthia and I would stay at my parents place for 2 of those weeks and prepare foods for them and encourage them to follow through. During this period we would also go on a walk or exercise for at least 30 minutes every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We told them about this “offer”. Although hesitant, my dad was eventually persuaded and accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the meal plan, the goal was to &lt;strong&gt;shift eating style from majority carbohydrates to 80% protein/fats and 20% carbohydrates. The carbohydrates were to have high fiber content (vegetable and fruits).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some more specific guidelines:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No rice, noodles, breads, or grains.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No dairy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Limit fruits (Berries ok)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Limit processed foods&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Berry/greens/fiber shake in the morning.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soy and Tofu is OK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beef, seafood, are OK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No vegetable oils&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coconut oil and olive oil OK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these guidelines, we wanted to match the meals to their taste. Meaning we incorporated asian ingredients and seasoning (soy sauce, tofu, ginger, etc) into the meals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;baseline&quot;&gt;Baseline&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are examples of my dad’s “standard” food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lunch-items&quot;&gt;Lunch items:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Breakfast_220611.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Egg, Banana, Beef Jerky, Cereal and Soy milk, Melon&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Breakfast_220612.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Steamed Bun, Sausage, Soy Milk, Fruit&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Lunch_220613.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Steamed Bun, Cereal, Fruit&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;dinner-items&quot;&gt;Dinner items:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Dinner_220611.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Beef Noodle Soup, Dried Beancurd with Pork&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Dinner_220613.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Dumpling, Scallion Pancake, Dried Beancurd with Pork&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/Jerry_Dinner_220618.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Sausage McMuffin, Hash Brown, Green Bean Soup, Shrimp and Bean, Fruit&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most days a significant portion (&amp;gt;50%) of my dad’s meals were composed of high-sugar food like noodles, breads, flour, and high-sugar fruits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-1-june-18-june-25&quot;&gt;Week 1 (June 18-June 25)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week 1 started with a trip to costco together. The highlights included pan-fried cod with ginger and soy sauce, lettuce wraps with fixings, and lots of tofu. We also incorporated some foods they already had in the fridge. Here are some of the photos:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/fish_bok_choy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Pan Fried Cod with Soy Sauce and Ginger, Bok choy, Tofu, Broccoli&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/salad_and_shrimp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Salad and Shrimp&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/lettuce_wrap_with_fixings.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Lettuce Wrap and Fixings (Tofu, Sirloin Strips, Pickled Veggies, Leftovers)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus was to &lt;strong&gt;shift away from carbohydrates-heavy foods and eat 80% protein and veggies.&lt;/strong&gt; Luckily a lot of the dishes and sides my parents liked were compatible for this food plan so it wasn’t too hard to adjust the menu and cooking. For example Zha Jiang Mian (Black bean sauce noodle) is something they ate regularly and had the sauce for. We substituted the usual noodles with shirataki noodles (made from konjac yam, contains minimal digestible carbohydrates). My mom also has a stash of fake meat products (mostly soy protein) that we incorporated into the meals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An added challenge was my dad eats meat but my mom is vegan. So we prepared vegan and nonvegan versions of dishes. You can see a lot of side dishes (and variety) in the pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also committed to go on a walk every evening after dinner. We talked about a range of topics from iphones + technology, diabetes and insulin pathways, Popeyes fried chicken, traveling, you name it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were a moments of low energy (likely due to the adjustment period and low blood sugar), but my parents remained very upbeat. &lt;strong&gt;Dad lost 6.6 lbs (3 kg) in the first week!&lt;/strong&gt; GJ dad!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-2-june-25-july-02&quot;&gt;Week 2 (June 25-July 02)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week 2 had more variety - highlights were Sop Buntut (Indonesian soup with spareribs and veggies), zha ziang mian using shirataki noodles, and vegetable curry. There were lots of sides as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/sop_buntut.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Sop Buntut (Indonesian Soup), Side Dishes&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/curry_veggies_eggs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Curry Veggies, Eggs, Shrimp&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/zha_jiang_mien_eggs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Zha Jiang Mien (Black Soybean Sauce Shirataki Noodles), Fried Egg, Cabbage, Tofu&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/basil_mushrooms.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Basil Mushrooms&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The parents were getting more into it and even contributed to making and preparing dishes. They were learning quickly about which foods were well-suited for this plan. We also demonstrated how to read a nutrition label and how to avoid picking things high in sugars/carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dad was interested in learning how to make the morning shake so I gave a demonstration. Pretty soon he was off and making his own shakes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/layer_juice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Berry and Greens shake&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/making_juice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Dad Preparing Shake&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By this time work was getting busy and the day-to-day included commuting to work one hour each way, cooking meals, going on a walk, then passing out. This period was exhausting but having Cynthia made it easier. It also helped that parents were learning and contributing. We realized the important thing was to continue building habits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-3-july-03-july-10&quot;&gt;Week 3 (July 03-July 10)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By week 3 the parents had the hang of things - Cynthia and I finished our stayover and let them to do their own thing. I checked in every few days to see what food they prepared and if they had kept up with exercise. My parents were very diligent and stuck to the plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every morning my dad would send a picture in our group chat showing off his weight displayed on the digital scale. It became the thing he was looking forward to the most each day because of the steady progress. I implemented a tracker on google sheets to log weight and exercise activity. With the aid of the bar chart, progress was easy to visualize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/weight_chart_zoom_in.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Weight over Time&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After three weeks of commitment to the plan with home cooked meals mostly every day it was time to celebrate. It was a great bonding time, and &lt;strong&gt;dad lost over 8.8 lbs (4 kg) in 3 weeks.&lt;/strong&gt; Here we are eating out in San Jose:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/eating_out_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Eating Out&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;        |
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;aftermath-august&quot;&gt;Aftermath (August)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dad continued to provide updates on his weight. My parents took parts of the 3 week program and continued on with it. For example, fruits were introduced but they continued to limit breads and grains, and went on walks nearly every day. My dad noticed stomach aches directly after drinking the morning shake, so we cut that out (We have a hunch it was due to stomach’s ability to process the high fiber amounts). Overall, It was even more exciting to see my dad continue to lose weight as a continuation of the plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/weight_chart_zoom_out.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Weight Chart&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Approximately a month after the program, my dad was under 82 kg, equating to &lt;strong&gt;15.4 lbs (7 kg) loss in 2 months!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also wanted to help my parents expand their exercise beyond walking. We decided to go to the park nearby to demonstrate some stretching and exercises (led by Cynthia).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/park_exercise.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Park Exercise&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;takeaways&quot;&gt;Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In retrospect this was a very successful visit and positive experience. Cynthia and I learned a great deal and got to spend quality time with my parents. My mom and dad built healthier habits, and continued to follow through even after the three week plan. On paper, the plan of limiting carbs and regular exercise was backed by science but what made it effective was getting the parents involved in process, the conversations during dinner and walks, and ultimately our presence and support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, Dad came with us to shop and purchase food. The act of us cooking and preparing meals allowed him plenty of chances to watch, and even critique us (lol).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the time parents had lots of questions. We had talks about nutrition labels, and what was considered nutritious and what was not (mostly processed sugars). We explained the mechanism in which the body processed sugar and what leads to diabetes (Link). Cynthia is the expert on health and has a lot of knowledge. My role was to support the conversation and translate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also &lt;strong&gt;very important&lt;/strong&gt; and probably the biggest factor: The parents were easy to work with and were very positive. They had an open mind going into this whole thing which was crucial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all it was a very positive experience and I’m confident we were able to build lasting habits/awareness on food!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some good resources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/carbohydrates/carbohydrates-and-blood-sugar/&quot;&gt;Harvard School of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6082688/&quot;&gt;The Carbohydrate-Insulin Model of Obesity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Diabetes-Code-Prevent-Reverse-Naturally/dp/1771642653&quot;&gt;The Diabetes Code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><description>&lt;!-- &lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;eight Loss&lt;/p&gt; --&gt;
</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/Parents-Visit/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/Parents-Visit/</guid></item><item>
        <title>First Elimination Diet</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;ver the past year I’ve been experimenting through diet. What kind of experiments you ask?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always had an interest in experimenting with food and diet. Through reading articles and hearing accounts from friends and colleagues, I’ve heard of the potential health benefits of improving the diet. I have dabbled in routines such as meatless Mondays and going beef-less although these were motivated more by wanting to reduce impact environmentally. However I had never put together a controlled diet used to explore my own health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I consider myself to be a healthy individual. I tend to cook 80% of my meals rather than eat out, and am, in my opinion, aware of what I consume and always try to exercise regularly through a mix of climbing, biking, body weight exercises. But in my latest lab results I found out I was prediabetic (A1C levels) which took me completely by surprise!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I’ve always had mysterious chronic symptoms that I could never understand. This includes inflammation of certain parts of skin and dryness in the throat. These have impacted things I love to do including climbing and singing so I felt compelled to understand but so far I’ve had little success in finding the root cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cynthia (my wife) studies functional medicine and reads about metabolism. We discuss these topics regularly and are aware of how important the gut microbiome is to overall body health. The whole concept makes perfect sense to me, as someone who works with microorganisms and designs fermentation experiments as part of my day job, I think of us as giant fermenters and that our microbes influence us more than we think. What we feed the microbes will obviously have a large impact on how we feel/behave. One takeaway is today’s diet has evolved to have so much more processed sugars and coincides with a steep rise of diabetes/obesity. Overwhelming amounts of research demonstrates these diseases are related to inflammation, and that the gut plays a huge role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cynthia proposed we do a elimination diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concept of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/healthy-weight/diet-reviews/anti-inflammatory-diet/&quot;&gt;elimination diet&lt;/a&gt; is this: remove foods commonly known to cause sensitivities in the gut. There are many variations of this out there (Whole30, low FODMAP) and ultimately it depends what the objective is. By removal of certain foods we can see how the gut, and the body, behaves in the absence of these foods. After a period, usually about 3 weeks of cleansing, certain foods would be &lt;strong&gt;re-introduced&lt;/strong&gt; and symptoms would be tracked to see if these symptoms could be pinpointed to certain foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However there were challenges to getting started. What recipes to use? How to source and prepare all of the foods? How to balance it with work/life? How bad was the experience going to be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;motivations&quot;&gt;Motivations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Health motivation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Would the chronic symptoms go away? Better yet could I discover what foods are linked to certain symptoms?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Experimentation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - this was an experiment and I was interested to see the effects for myself. Self-Process development y’all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Challenge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; – See if I could follow through. I knew from the get-go it would require a lot of planning and changes to habits. I like food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;plan-details&quot;&gt;Plan Details&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 21-day gut cleansing diet with these guiding points:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No grains (rice, bread, noodles,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No gluten (bread, flour, soy sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No legumes (chickpeas, lentils, beans)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No dairy (butter, milk, cheese)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heavy limit on added sugars&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No fructose (only berries)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No eggs (specific to me, food sensitivity)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No soy (Tofu, soy sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No processed foods&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No to certain oils (canola, vegetable)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes fish, chicken, pork, beef&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes berries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes leafy greens&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes mushrooms&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes to certain nuts (almonds, macademia)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yes olive oil, coconut oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holy moly that’s a lot of restrictions! In addition:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Supplements of saccharomyces.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Digestion aids.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Magnesium&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Berbere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reintroduction phase would focus on 4 foods/main areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Eggs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dairy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wheat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;So how did it go?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-1&quot;&gt;Week 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week 1 was all about acclimation and the body adjusting to these different meals and snacks. Some of these required more effort to adapt to due my chocolate/fruit eating habit. We had chocolate berry smoothies in the morning, and celery/carrots for snacks. The first big meals consisted of herb baked fish and tomato soup, as well as turkey lettuce wraps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/turkey_wrap.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Lettuce Wrap with Turkey + Squash + Veggies&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/herb_fish.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Pan Fried Fish with spices + Cauliflower Rice&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/maitake.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Cooked Maitake Mushrooms&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I immediately noticed there was no sleepiness/grogginess after meals, or any desire to take naps (which is unusual for me). The feeling of food comas after meals went away completely. The first few days I was peeing a lot and had to replenish by drinking lots of water. Also there was no bloating whatsoever after meals which was a revelation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another observation - it was tough to control snacking. I realized how many snacks I eat at work (as someone who takes full advantage of this)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-2&quot;&gt;Week 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt the fruits of the labor kicking in. This week I had the best poo of my life. Energy was very good throughout the week - I describe it as a continuous hum of energy. I had expected to feel less energetic in physical activities such as climbing but my performance was as good as ever. I also discovered new snacks (carrots and celery sticks with almond butter gets old pretty fast). Masala peas from Berkeley Bowl!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/avocado_salad.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Avocado Salad&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/roast_salmon.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Roast Salmon&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/snacks1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Snacks&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;week-3&quot;&gt;Week 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things got tougher in the 3rd week. I noticed my enthusiasm was slowing down due to eating a lot of salads for meals. I also noticed I was getting cranky - I blame this on excessivly low sugar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/almond_chicken.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Chicken with Almond Butter Sauce&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/roast_mushrooms.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Oven roasted Mushrooms&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/roast_veggies1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; 
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Roasted Veggies&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reintroduction&quot;&gt;Reintroduction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We introduced the following foods back into diet. 2 days on for each type of food then 3 days off before reintroducing the next food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Eggs. There were stomach pains after the first meal with eggs. It only seemed to be problem for the first meal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tofu. Felt fine except for one meal where we overstuffed with too much tofu during hotpot.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dairy. No issues.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wheat. Felt sleepy the whole day. Unsure if it was due to excess carbs or traceable to gluten.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;summary-of-observations&quot;&gt;Summary of observations:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the course of this experiment we tracked and quantified things such as headaches, severity of acne, bowel movement…etc. We even tried quantifying some more subjective things such as energy levels, irritability, and focus. Here were the main observations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Energy - I felt like I could keep going most days in terms of work/schoolwork/daily tasks. A constant hum is how I describe it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Physical Performance – Felt really good, as good as I’ve ever felt. Could climb at the same levels and do the same amount of pullups.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Irritability – By the end, Inoticed I was getting crankier.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weight loss - No change any weight. Cynthia lost 9 lbs in 6 weeks!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;was-the-diet-successful&quot;&gt;Was the diet successful?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I discover any foods that explained symptoms! Yes! It was a rich learning experience and I definitely found links for types of foods that affected energy levels. And bloatiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did it cure all of my mystery chronic symptoms? No - although I wasn’t expecting to figure out the answer to all my problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Increased awareness - Now I do more research when choosing foods and check ingredient labels for everything. I have much more awareness on what foods contain sugars and carbs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw firsthand positive effects of eating less sugar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really like the increased energy and ‘cleaner’ feeling digestion. I used to get upset stomach that would immobilize me/make me want to lie down certain days. I felt a more consistent ‘good’ energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other-takeways&quot;&gt;Other takeways:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Challenges in execution – it takes A LOT of effort to come up with a plan for meals and follow through. More on this later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be deliberate in what sugars to eat. I’ll still eat sugar, but will avoid white processed sugar, white bread. I used to have unlimited allowance of sugars but now I will track/limit my intake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating salads repeatedly can get old. Variety is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal goal to shift diet to more veggies. For meals I used to have 30% protein, 50% carbs, 20% veggies. Now my goal is to have 40% protein, 40% veggies, 20% carbs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/nutritionsource/healthy-weight/diet-reviews/anti-inflammatory-diet/&quot;&gt;Harvard School of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><description>&lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;ver the past year I’ve been experimenting through diet. What kind of experiments you ask?&lt;/p&gt;
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/First-Elimination-Diet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/First-Elimination-Diet/</guid></item></channel>
</rss>
